skincareresourcecenter.com 2016-03-16

# Disclaimer Statement

We do not endorse any specific products, companies,   
strategies, techniques, regimens or treatments.   

The privacy of our visitors to the skincareresourcecenter.com   
is important to us.  

Privacy Policy

At The Skin Care e-Learning and Resource Center, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information are received and collected when you use visit The Skin Care e-Learning and Resource Center, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use The Skin Care Resource Center, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us. The Skin Care Resource Center strives to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to protecting our customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on our website.

Personal Information:  
The Skin Care Resource Center collects personally identifiable information from the visitors to our website only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number. This information is collected if you request information from us, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, and sign up to join our email list or request some other service or information from us. 

The information collected is internally reviewed, used to improve the content of our website, notify our visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries. Once information is reviewed, it is discarded or stored in our files. If we make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information we will inform you by placing a notice on our site. Personal information received from any visitor will be used only for internal purposes and will not be sold or provided to third parties. 

Affiliate Programs:  
When you choose to make a purchase for a product via a link I recommend on this site, I earn a small commission. These commissions fund the site in order to keep it up and running.

I am a participant in several affiliate programs including Google, LinkShare, Commission Junction, Share-a-Sale, and the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program.  These affiliate companies are affiliate advertising programs designed to provide a means for sites to earn commission and advertising fees by advertising and linking to products like those on Amazon.com.

Log Files:  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

Cookies and Web Beacons:  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We also use third party advertisements on The Skin Care e-Learning and Resource Center to support our site. 

Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

  We may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. 

For example, if you personalize the sites pages, or register with any of our site's services, a cookie enables The Skin Care Resource Center to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your Web browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site. 

A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single website or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs and are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a web site. 

We may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons in the course of ads being served on our web site to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. 

No personally identifiable information you give us is provided to them for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on our web site. 

Some third-party advertisements may be provided by Google, which uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses the DART cookie, which enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Managing Privacy and Cookies:  
You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

  Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with our site, should you so choose. 

Google Search Boxes:  
The search boxes on this web site ("Search Box") are  powered by Google Inc ("Google"). Google requires that you acknowledge and agree that Google's privacy policy (located at http://www.google.co.uk/privacy.html) shall apply to your use of the Search Box and by using the Search Box you consent to Google using your personal data in accordance with its privacy policy.

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act:  
This website is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. We operate our site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and will not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

Non-Personal Information:  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

The information collected is used solely for internal review and not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

Release of Information:  
If The Skin Care Resource Center is sold, the information we have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale in order that the service being provided to you may continue. 

In that event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make of us. 

How You Can Correct or Remove Information:  
We provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of our commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through our website and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please use our Contact Us page to inform us of your decision. 

Updates and Effective Date:  
The Skin Care Resource Center reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on our site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it. 

Agreeing to Terms:  
If you do not agree to The Skin Care Resource Center's Privacy Policy as posted here on this website, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site. Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
